easywebvideo.com 2009-03-13

# Easy Web Video Privacy Policy

At TopNet Solutions, Inc. we know that privacy is important. This brief document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use our site and software, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. 

**Personal information and other data**

We never collect or store any credit card or other sensitive payment information after you place an order. This is all handled between you and our trusted 3rd party payment processor (clickbank.com) to protect our valued customers. After your order is placed the only information we collect is your email address in order to assist you with your purchase. We also ask that you sign up for an update notification list to receive email updates about your software. This update notification list is managed by another trusted third party (aweber.com) and you have the ability to opt out any any time by following the link at the bottom of any email we send you.

TopNet Solutions, Inc. uses cookies and other technologies to track the performance of our valued affiliates in order to ensure they receive proper credit when referring visitors to the site. A cookie is simply a small file placed on your computer that tells us that you came to us from a particular affiliate. 

**Uses  **

We may use personal information such as your email address to provide you with related offers as they apply to this specific product. Only related offers will be sent to those that signup for our software updates, and you can unsubscribe at any time. 

**Your choices  **

You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result. 

We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible. 

If you have additional questions, please contact us any time.
